teliasonera.com 2010-12-10

# Privacy | TeliaSonera

## Your privacy at [www.teliasonera.com](http://www.teliasonera.com/)

TeliaSonera appreciates your interest in the company and your visit to the company website. Your privacy is important to us and we want you to feel safe when using this website. TeliaSonera strives to offer Internet services that do not compromise the privacy of customers and visitors.

TeliaSonera has secure networks that are protected with firewalls and passwords. We have taken several safety-enhancing measures to protect the personal data in our possession from loss, misuse and alteration. We for example log IP numbers in order to prevent misuse.

Only a handful of our employees have access to the personal data you leave with us. TeliaSonera has implemented very strict rules for the employees who have access to the databases that store user information or to the servers that host our services. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur, we work actively to prevent such occurrences.

### Handling of personal data

TeliaSonera handles personal data in accordance with what is laid down in the Swedish acts on personal data (personuppgiftslagen SFS 1998:204) and electronic communications (lagen om elektronisk kommunikation SFS 2003:389).

Both of these acts include provisions aiming at the protection of private persons from violations against their personal integrity in the processing of personal data.

The personal information you leave at our website is used only to send you information concerning your choices in for example the subscription services or job seeking sections.

### Disclosure of personal data to a third party

Certain data may be processed by partners of TeliaSonera to the extent they are involved in fulfilling the contract between the customer and TeliaSonera.

## Information about cookies

The TeliaSonera website uses cookies. A cookie is a small text file stored in your computer containing text data. Cookies are used for certain functions improving the usability of the website. We do not store personal data in cookies and we cannot trace information back to you on the basis of the cookies.

TeliaSonera websites use two types of cookies. The first is a permanent file stored in your computer. It enables information which has changed since your last visit to be updated. If you have previously visited the site, the unchanged information is retrieved locally from your computer. This enables you to access the information on the home page more quickly.

The other cookie type is called a session cookie. The server sends a session cookie to your computer for the duration of the session, enabling information such as your choice of language to be transmitted. Session cookies are not stored in your computer; they are removed automatically when you close your web browser.

### Enabling or disabling cookies

You can choose whether you wish to accept cookies or not. Most web browsers (e.g. Internet Explorer and Netscape) enable cookies automatically, but you may change the settings to disable all cookies or to enable/disable them one by one. If cookies are disabled, your use of the website and its services will be limited. For more information on how to change your cookie settings, please consult the Help menu of the browser.

## Other information

"Other information" refers to impersonal data. We use such information on TeliaSonera websites. The data includes website visiting times, access times, browser versions, operating systems and other information unrelated to the user. This information helps us to keep track of our visitors, for example how long they visit different pages. With this information, we can improve the efficiency and composition of our website. TeliaSonera registers this kind of information on all the visitors on our websites, not just on our registered customers and members.
